chatfuel.com 2018-10-05

# Information You Provide to Us:

If you are an EU resident, our ​EU specific Privacy Policy​ applies to you.
                                            Privacy Policy
Effective date: ​September 21, 2018
We at Chatfuel know you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we
take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy.
By using or accessing the Services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the
practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will
collect, use, and share your information in the following ways.
Remember that your​ use of Chatfuel’s Services is at all times subject to the ​Terms of Use​, which
incorporates this Privacy Policy. Any terms we use in this Policy without defining them have the
definitions given to them in the ​Terms of Use​.
What does this Privacy Policy cover​?
This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal
Information") that we gather when you are accessing or using our Services, but not to the
practices of companies we don’t own or control, or people that we don’t manage. We gather
various types of Personal Information from our users, as explained in more detail below, and we
use this Personal Information internally in connection with our Services, including to personalize,
provide, and improve our services, to allow you to set up a user account, to enable you to build
chatbots and communicate with chatbots others have built, to contact you and allow other users to
contact you, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to analyze how you use
the Services. In certain cases, we may also share some Personal Information with third parties,
but only as described below.
As noted in the ​Terms of Use​, we do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from
anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Services
or send any personal information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal
information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If
you believe that a child under 13 may have provided us personal information, please contact us at
tos@chatfuel.com​.
Will Chatfuel ever change this Privacy Policy​?
We’re constantly trying to improve our Services, so we may need to change this Privacy Policy
from time to time as well, but we will alert you to changes by placing a notice on Chatfuel.com,
by sending you an email, and/or by some other means. Please note that if you’ve opted not to
receive legal notice emails from us (or you haven’t provided us with your email address), those
legal notices will still govern your use of the Services, and you are still responsible for reading
and understanding them. If you use the Services after any changes to the Privacy Policy have
been posted, that means you agree to all of the changes. Use of information we collect now is
subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used.
What Information does Chatfuel Collect​?
Information You Provide to Us:

If you are an EU resident, our ​EU specific Privacy Policy​ applies to you.
We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us. For example, if you create an
account on our Services to build a chatbot, through the registration process and/or through your
account settings, we may collect Personal Information such as, but not limited to, your name,
email address, timezone, list of Facebook Pages you own. Or, if you are an individual who
communicates with chatbots that have been created using our services, we may collect
information such as, but not limited to, your name, gender, time zone, and avatar/picture. If you
provide your Facebook or other third-party account credentials to, you understand some content
and/or information in those accounts (“Third Party Account Information”) may be transmitted
into your account with us, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Services is
covered by this Privacy Policy; for example, when you log in to our Services using your
Facebook Messenger account, we may receive your personal information associated with that
account, such as your Facebook pages. Certain information may be required to register with us or
to take advantage of some of our features.
Information Collected Automatically
Whenever you interact with our Services, we automatically receive and record information on our
server logs from your browser or device, which may include any chatbots you have created using
the Services, your conversation history with the chatbots(s), IP address, geolocation data, device
identification, “cookie” information, the type of browser and/or device you’re using to access our
Services, and the page or feature you requested. “Cookies” are identifiers we transfer to your
browser or device that allow us to recognize your browser or device and tell us how and when
pages and features in our Services are visited and by how many people. You may be able to
change the preferences on your browser or device to prevent or limit your device’s acceptance of
cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our features.
If you click on a link to a third party website or service, a third party may also transmit cookies to
you. Again, this Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties, and we
aren’t responsible for their privacy policies and practices. Please be aware that cookies placed by
third parties may continue to track your activities online even after you have left our Services, and
those third parties may not honor “Do Not Track” requests you have set using your browser or
device.
We may use this data to customize content for you that we think you might like, based on your
usage patterns. We may also use it to improve the Services or to help developers build better
chatbots– for example, this data can tell us how often users use a particular feature of the
Services, or what kinds of questions users ask of certain chatbots, and we can use that knowledge
to make the Services and the chatbots created through the Services interesting to as many users as
possible.
Information Collected From Other Websites and Do Not Track Policy
Through cookies we place on your browser or device, we may collect information about your
online activity after you leave our Services. Just like any other usage information we collect, this
information allows us to improve the Services and customize your online experience, and
otherwise as described in this Privacy Policy. Your browser may offer you a “Do Not Track”
option, which allows you to signal to operators of websites and web applications and services
(including behavioral advertising services) that you do not wish such operators to track certain of

If you are an EU resident, our ​EU specific Privacy Policy​ applies to you.
your online activities over time and across different websites. We honor Do Not Track signals
from your browser.
What information does Chatfuel processes in connection with third party services?
Depending on how you have configured our Services, you may be able to use several
functionalities provided by third parties. Certain of these functions need further information or
personal data processed by us or the third party. Please note that you as our customer remain
solely responsible under applicable data protection law for the processing of personal data under
such functionality to your user and we remain the processor of such data. The fulfilment of
obligations under applicable data protection law to your users is thus solely your responsibility.
We will provide information on any of our products and services in this regard in the following:
Transfer data with our Services to Google sheets​:
Our Services provide the functionality to send data to Google sheets provided by a messenger
chatbot you have built with our Services. You can provide content to the Google sheets and share
certain information, e.g., bot user’s email address. If you want to use this function, the processing
of certain data is mandatory to provide the functionality and will be done on your behalf only. For
this purpose, we collect and process personal data, in particular, the Google ID or email address.
In addition, we collect technical data, such as access tokens, refresh tokens or spreadsheet IDs.
All information we collect is processed solely to provide the functionality as described above.
Except for bot admin’s email address, which could possibly be shared with other admins to the
extent necessary to provide this function, none of the processed data is being shared with third
parties other than elsewhere stated in this privacy policy.
To comply with the data protection obligations, we recommend informing your users on the
processing by adding the following wording to your privacy policy, without giving any warranty
to be sufficient to comply with the legal obligations to which you are subject:
“We collect or process personal data by the use of third-party tools, inter alia, we use the
services of 200 Labs, Inc. d/b/a Chatfuel (“Chatfuel”). Chatfuel is an online platform that allows
us to easily build, host and manage chatbots. We use certain functionalities that enable us to send
data to Google sheets provided by a messenger chatbot we have built with Chatfuel’s services.
Using this function, the processing of certain data by Chatfuel and Google is mandatory to
provide the functionality. For this purpose, we may collect and process personal data, such as
email addresses. In addition, we collect technical data, such as access tokens, refresh tokens or
spreadsheet IDs. All information we collect is processed solely to provide the functionality as
described above. None of the processed data is being shared with third parties other than already
stated in this privacy policy.”
Will Chatfuel Share Any of the Personal Information it Receives​?
We do not rent or sell your Personal Information in personally identifiable form to anyone. We
may share your Personal Information with third parties as described in this section:
Information that’s been de-identified. ​We may de-identify your Personal Information so that
you are not identified as an individual, and provide that information to our partners. We may also
provide aggregate usage information to our partners (or allow partners to collect that information

If you are an EU resident, our ​EU specific Privacy Policy​ applies to you.
from you), who may use such information to understand how often and in what ways people use
our Services, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal online experience. However, we
never disclose aggregate usage or de-identified information to a partner (or allow a partner to
collect such information) in a manner that would identify you as an individual person.
Chatbot Developers: ​The developers/owners of chatbots created through the Services which you
communicate with will have access to the Personal Information you provide to them. For
example, if you communicate with a chatbot which was created through the Services, the
developer/owner of that chatbot may have access to your conversation history with the chatbot,
your username, your avatar, and any other information you provide through the chatbot. In
addition, the chatbot developer/owner may use a Salesforce or other third party product
integration to receive and process the data from your interaction with the chatbot.
Affiliated Businesses: In certain situations, businesses or third party websites we’re affiliated
with may sell or provide products or services to you through or in connection with the Services
(either alone or jointly with us). You can recognize when an affiliated business is associated with
such a transaction or service, and we will share your Personal Information with that affiliated
business only to the extent that it is related to such transaction or service. One such service may
include the ability for you to automatically transmit Third Party Account Information, such as
your Facebook Messenger profile information, to your Services profile or to automatically
transmit information in your Services profile to your third party account. We have no control
over the policies and practices of third party websites or businesses as to privacy or anything else,
so if you choose to take part in any transaction or service relating to an affiliated website or
business, please review all such business’ or websites’ policies.
Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share
your information with them to provide products or services to you; for example, we may use a
payment processing company to receive and process your credit card transactions for us. Unless
we tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share
with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. Note that an “agent” may also be considered a
“partner” in certain circumstances, and would be subject to the terms of the “​Information that’s
been de-identified​” section in that regard.
Business Transfers: We may choose to buy or sell assets, and may share and/or transfer
customer information in connection with the evaluation of and entry into such transactions. A  ​ lso,
if we (or our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through
some other change of control, Personal Information could be one of the assets transferred to or
acquired by a third party.
Protection of Chatfuel and Others: We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose
any information that we believe is necessary to comply with law or court order; enforce or apply
our ​Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Chatfuel, our
employees, our users, or others.
Is Personal Information about me secure​?
Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. If you access your
account via Facebook or another third party site or service, you may have additional or different

If you are an EU resident, our ​EU specific Privacy Policy​ applies to you.
sign-on protections via that third party site or service. You must prevent unauthorized access to
your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password and/or other
sign-on mechanism appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by
signing off after you have finished accessing your account.
We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other Personal Information we hold in
our records, but unfortunately, we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or
use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user
information at any time.
Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to
contact us to prevent disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for such third parties’
direct marketing purposes; in order to submit such a request, please contact us at
tos@chatfuel.com​.
What choices do I have​?
You can always opt not to disclose information to us, but keep in mind some information may be
needed to register with us, to communicate with chatbots, or to take advantage of some of our
features.
You may stop using the Services at any time; however, your conversation logs from
communications with chatbots may remain in our records.
What if I have questions about this policy?
If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send us a detailed
message to ​tos@chatfuel.com​, and we will try to resolve your concerns.
